Guide to the Robert Penn Warren Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Writings, 1930-85; Series II; 60; (145 boxes)
  - BOOKS
    - John Brown: The Making of a Martyr
      - Holograph notes, n.d. (Box 153, Folder 2770)
      - First Draft
        - Copy 1: typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 153, Folder 2771-76)
        - Copy 2 (marked "first draft"): typescript,carbon, corrected, n.d. (Box 153, Folder 2777-83)
        - Copy 3: typescript, carbon, corrected, n.d. (Box 153, Folder 2784-89)
      - Reviews, 1930, n.d. (Box 153, Folder 2790-92)
    - John Greenleaf Whittier's Poetry
      - Source material, 1954, n.d. (Box 154, Folder 2793-94)
      - Introduction
        - Draft A: holograph, n.d. (Box 154, Folder 2795)
        - Draft B: typescript, carbon, n.d. (Box 154, Folder 2796)
        - Draft C (with notes to poems): typescript, corrected, 1967 (Box 154, Folder 2797)
        - Draft D (revised draft): typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 154, Folder 2798-99)
        - Draft E (for Sewanee Review printing, marked "final"): typescript, corrected, [1971] (Box 154, Folder 2800-01)
        - Draft fragments: typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 154, Folder 2802)
      - Reviews, 1971 (Box 154, Folder 2803)
      - Letter to the editor of Whittier Newsletter explaining and defending Warren's commentaries: typescript and carbons, 1973 (Box 154, Folder 2804-05)
    - Kentucky Mountain Farm and Other Poems (unpublished)
      - Typescript, carbon, n.d. (Box 154, Folder 2806)
    - Legacy of the Civil War
      - Source material, 1962 Aug 5 (Box 154, Folder 2807)
      - Holograph notes, n.d. (Box 154, Folder 2808)
      - Life version
        - Draft A ("First draft," incomplete): typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 154, Folder 2809)
        - Draft B (marked "third version," but with notation that this was "the first short version made for Life "): typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 154, Folder 2810)
        - Draft C (marked "working draft," incomplete): typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 154, Folder 2811)
        - Draft D (revised draft): typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 154, Folder 2812)
        - "Rejected leaves": holograph and typescript (Box 154, Folder 2813)
        - Long version
          - Draft A: typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 154, Folder 2814)
          - Draft B: typescript, carbon, corrected, n.d. (Box 155, Folder 2815)
        - Fragments: typescript, carbon, corrected, n.d. (Box 155, Folder 2816)
        - "Footnotes not included in text": typescript, n.d. (Box 155, Folder 2817)
        - Setting typescript, corrected, 1961 (Box 155, Folder 2818)
        - Layout sheets, n.d. (Box 155, Folder 2819)
        - Galley proofs
          See: Oversize, Box 295, folders 5255-57
        - Page proofs
          See: Oversize, Box 295, folder 5258
        - Plate proofs
          See: Oversize, Box 295, folder 5259
        - "Le Guerre de Sécession Contient les clefs de L'Amerique" (excerpt). Le Figaro Litteraire., 1962 Jun 16 (Box 155, Folder 2820)
        - Reviews, 1961 (Box 155, Folder 2821-23)
    - Listen to the Mockingbird ( The Wedding Ring )
      - Draft A
        - Copy 1: typescript, carbon, n.d. (Box 156, Folder 2824)
        - Copy 2 (marked "version A"), typescript, carbon, n.d. (Box 156, Folder 2825)
        - Copy 3 (marked "old version"): typescript, carbon, n.d. (Box 156, Folder 2826)
        - Copy 4: typescript, carbon, corrected, n.d. (Box 156, Folder 2827)
        - Copy 5 (stamped "Eric Bentley"): typescript, carbon, n.d. (Box 156, Folder 2828)
        - Copy 6 (marked "early version"): typescript, carbon, n.d. (Box 156, Folder 2829)
        - Copy 7 (listed as "A Play by Robert Penn Warren and Robert Rossen"; marked "early version"): typescript, carbon (Box 156, Folder 2830)
        - Draft A "Early version Wedding Ring, reading for Robert Rossen" (1 of 2 audiotape reels), undated; 1; 01:04:30; The program is distorted at times. High background noise can be heard on the tape. (Box 334, Item barcode 39002099360134)
        - Draft A "Early version Wedding Ring, reading for Robert Rossen" (2 of 2 audiotape reels), undated; 1; 01:04:35; The program is distorted at times. High background noise can be heard on the tape. Static can also be heard. (Box 334, Item barcode 39002099360142)
      - Draft B: typescript, carbon, n.d. (Box 157, Folder 2831-32)
      - Draft C (incomplete): typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 157, Folder 2833)
      - Draft D: typescript, carbon, [1955] (Box 157, Folder 2834)
      - Draft E: typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 157, Folder 2835)
      - Draft F (marked "Master Draft"): typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 157, Folder 2836-38)
      - Draft G (marked "version B-unrevised"): typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 157, Folder 2839)
      - Draft H (marked "version B," incomplete): typescript, carbon, n.d. (Box 157, Folder 2840)
      - Draft I (marked "version C"): typescript, carbon, 1955 (Box 157, Folder 2841)
      - Draft J (marked "version C"-- "intermediate version"--incomplete): typescript, carbon, corrected, n.d. (Box 157, Folder 2842)
      - Draft K (incomplete: Act I, Scene i only): typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 157, Folder 2843)
      - Draft L
        - Copy 1: typescript, carbon, n.d. (Box 158, Folder 2844)
        - Copy 2: typescript, carbon, corrected, n.d. (Box 158, Folder 2845)
      - Draft M (marked "worksheets," incomplete): typescript, corrected, with holograph notes, 1955 (Box 158, Folder 2846)
      - Draft N: typescript, carbon, n.d. (Box 158, Folder 2847-49)
      - "Worksheets" (to preceding draft ?): typescript, n.d. (Box 158, Folder 2850)
      - Draft O: typescript, carbon, [1959] (Box 158, Folder 2851)
      - Draft P (marked "version D"): typescript, carbon, corrected, 1959 Jun (Box 158, Folder 2852)
      - Draft Q (with Lawrence Langer's name): typescript, carbon, corrected, n.d. (Box 158, Folder 2853-55)
      - Draft R
        - Copy 1 (marked "Lawrence Langner's copy," with letter critiquing play by Vincent Donahue): typescript, carbon, corrected, 1960 (Box 158, Folder 2856)
        - Copy 2: typescript, carbon, 1960 (Box 159, Folder 2857)
      - Draft S: typescript, carbon, n.d. (Box 159, Folder 2858)
      - Rejected leaves (with outlines for revision of Act III): typescript, 1959, n.d. (Box 159, Folder 2859-60)
      - Manuscript fragments: holograph and typescript, 1960, n.d. (Box 159, Folder 2861-64)
    - Love in the Valley
      - Source material (marked "legal material"), 1970, n.d. (Box 160, Folder 2865)
      - Holograph notes, n.d. (Box 160, Folder 2866-69)
      - Draft A: holograph, 1963, n.d. (Box 160, Folder 2870-81)
      - Draft B (marked "not a proper first draft.. ."): typescript, n.d. (Box 160, Folder 2882-85)
      - Draft B (marked "not a proper first draft.. ."): typescript, n.d. (Box 161, Folder 2886-91)
      - Draft C
        - Copy 1: typescript, carbon, 1963 (Box 161, Folder 2892-99)
        - Copy 2 (incomplete): typescript, carbon, 1963 (Box 162, Folder 2900-01)
        - Copy 3 (incomplete): typescript, carbon, 1963 (Box 162, Folder 2902-03)
      - Draft D: typescript, n.d. (Box 162, Folder 2904-06)
      - Draft E (includes multiple versions of several chapters): typescript and photocopy (Box 162, Folder 2907-17)
      - Draft E (includes multiple versions of several chapters): typescript and photocopy (Box 163, Folder 2918-25)
      - Draft F
        - Copy 1 (marked "first complete draft," with comments by Eleanor Clark): typescript, photocopy, n.d. (Box 163, Folder 2926-33)
        - Copy 1 (marked "first complete draft," with comments by Eleanor Clark): typescript, photocopy, n.d. (Box 164, Folder 2934-35)
        - Copy 2 (marked "Draft-Spring-1970"): typescript, photocopy (Box 164, Folder 2936-42)
      - Draft G (with Warren's corrections and holograph revision of chapter XII and suggested changes by Pier Pasinetti?): typescript, photocopy, corrected (Box 164, Folder 2943-49)
      - Draft G (with Warren's corrections and holograph revision of chapter XII and suggested changes by Pier Pasinetti?): typescript, photocopy, corrected, 1969, n.d. (Box 165, Folder 2950-52)
      - Draft H (incomplete): typescript, photocopy, corrected, [1971] (Box 165, Folder 2953)
      - Revision sheets: typescript, carbon, n.d. (Box 165, Folder 2954)
      - Manuscript fragment ("version as of Nov. 16," portion of Chapter X only, with letter from Jordan Stokes): typescript, corrected, 1970 (Box 165, Folder 2955)
      - Discarded manuscript pages, n.d. (Box 165, Folder 2956)
      - Setting typescript, 1971 (Box 165, Folder 2957-65)
      - Layout sheets (incomplete), n.d. (Box 166, Folder 2966)
      - "Blues" (incomplete), n.d. (Box 166, Folder 2967)
      - "Van-Dykes" (Box 166, Folder 2968-70)
      - Editorial material (Random House), 1971 (Box 166, Folder 2971)
      - Related Correspondence, 1969-71 (Box 166, Folder 2972-73)
      - Reviews, 1971=72 (Box 166, Folder 2974-75)
      - Critical studies
        - Lee, Young-Oak, "Misguided Illusion: The Blithdale Romance and Meet Me in the Green Glen (offprint) (Box 166, Folder 2976)
      - Miscellaneous, n.d. (Box 166, Folder 2977)
    - Modern Rhetoric (Fourth Edition)
      - Draft A: typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 166, Folder 2978-82)
      - Draft A: typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 167, Folder 2983-87)
      - Draft B (incomplete, with corrections by Cleanth Brooks): printed text (photocopy) and typescript (photocopy) (Box 167, Folder 2988-89)
      - Draft fragment (with corrections by Cleanth Brooks): typescript, n.d. (Box 167, Folder 2990)
      - Instructor's Manual: typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 167, Folder 2991-93)
      - Setting typescript, n.d. (Box 167, Folder 2994-95)
      - Setting typescript, n.d. (Box 168, Folder 2996-3003)
    - Modern Rhetoric (Shorter Fourth Edition)
      - Revised Draft: typescript, photocopy, corrected, n.d. (Box 168, Folder 3004-08)
    - New and Selected Essays
      - Reviews, 1989 (Box 169, Folder 3009)
    - New and Selected Poems, 1923-1985
      - Tentative list of contents, n.d. (Box 169, Folder 3010)
      - Table of contents, n.d. (Box 169, Folder 3011)
      - List of poems appearing in magazines: typescript, n.d. (Box 169, Folder 3012)
      - Preface to Franklin Mint edition (with abridgement for New York Times Review of Books ): holograph and typescript, corrected (Box 169, Folder 3013)
      - Various early drafts, 1981-82, n.d. (Box 169, Folder 3014-15)
      - Typescript and photocopy, corrected (incomplete) (Box 169, Folder 3016-17)
      - Typescript (incomplete) with comments by Cleanth Brooks, n.d. (Box 169, Folder 3018)
      - Setting typescript, corrected (with photocopy sheets), n.d. (Box 169, Folder 3019-24)
      - Setting typescript, revised (incomplete), n.d. (Box 169, Folder 3025)
      - Copyright and acknowledgement pages: photocopy (Box 169, Folder 3026)
      - Galley proofs
        See: Oversize, Box 298, folders 5269-72 and Box 299, folders 5273-77
      - Page proofs
        See: Oversize, Box 300, folder 5278
      - Revised page proofs (incomplete), n.d. (Box 169, Folder 3027)
      - "Repros," uncorrected, n.d. (Box 170, Folder 3028-30)
      - "Repros," revised (incomplete), n.d. (Box 170, Folder 3031)
      - "Repros," corrected, [1985] (Box 170, Folder 3032-36)
      - "Blues", [1985] (Box 170, Folder 3037-38)
      - "Advance Uncorrected Proofs" (with Warren's annotations): printed text, n.d. (Box 170, Folder 3039)
      - Table of contents: printed text, photocopy, n.d. (Box 170, Folder 3040)
      - "Original text for Finland edition": typescript, corrected (Box 170, Folder 3041)
      - Manuscript for Finland edition: typescript, photocopy (Box 171, Folder 3042)
      - Reviews, 1985 (Box 171, Folder 3043-44)
      - Critical studies
        - Runyon, Randolph. "'The Distance Between': Sequence and Simultaneity in Warren: Altitudes and Extensions": typescript (Box 171, Folder 3045)
    - Night Rider
      - Reviews (Box 171, Folder 3046-47)
      - Critical Studies
        - Law, Richard. "Warren's Night Rider and the Issue of Naturalism...." The Southern Literary Journal, 1976 Spring (Box 171, Folder 3048)
        - Ryan, Alvin S. "Robert Penn Warren's Night Rider ," Modern Fiction Studies (offprint), 1962 (Box 171, Folder 3049)
    - Now and Then
      - List of poems, n.d. (Box 171, Folder 3050)
      - Early drafts (mixed): holograph and typescript, corrected, 1976-77, n.d. (Box 171, Folder 3051-54)
      - Revised draft: typescript and photocopies, 1977 (Box 171, Folder 3055-56)
      - Typescript, corrected (marked "Master Copy") (Box 171, Folder 3057)
      - Setting typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 171, Folder 3058)
      - Galley proofs
        See: Oversize, box 301, folder 5282-83
      - Page proofs
        See: Oversize, box 301, folder 5284
      - "Repros"
        - Copy 1: corrected (Box 171, Folder 3059)
        - Copy 2: "set 2, untouched" (Box 171, Folder 3060)
      - "Blues" (Box 171, Folder 3061)
      - Layouts for front matter, n.d. (Box 171, Folder 3062)
      - Editorial material (Random House), 1978 (Box 172, Folder 3063-64)
      - Related correspondence, 1976-78 (Box 172, Folder 3065)
      - Reviews, 1978-79 (Box 172, Folder 3066-68)
      - Miscellaneous, 1979 (Box 172, Folder 3069)
    - Or Else ("Essay Toward the Human Understanding")
      - Draft A (early draft, incomplete): holograph and typescript (Box 172, Folder 3070-78)
      - Draft B (incomplete): typescript, corrected, 1969, n.d. (Box 172, Folder 3079)
      - Draft C: typescript, photocopy, corrected, 1973 (Box 172, Folder 3080-1)
      - Setting typescript
        - Copy 1: typescript, photocopy, corrected, n.d. (Box 172, Folder 3082)
        - Copy 2: typescript, photocopy, n.d. (Box 172, Folder 3083)
      - Galley proofs
        See: Oversize, Box 301, folders 5285-86
      - Page proofs
        See: Oversize, box 301, folders 5287-89
      - "Repros"
        - Copy 1 ("touched-up"), n.d. (Box 172, Folder 3084)
        - Copy 2 ("set 2: untouched"), n.d. (Box 172, Folder 3085)
      - "Blues" (Box 173, Folder 3086)
      - Editorial material, 1974 (Box 173, Folder 3087)
      - Related correspondence, 1974 (Box 173, Folder 3088)
      - Critical studies
        - Parker, Theodore. "The Disintegrating Subject of Morality In Robert Penn Warren's Or Else...." (dissertaton with comments by Warren): typescript, 1984 (Box 173, Folder 3089)
      - Reviews, 1974 (Box 174, Folder 3090-91)
    - A Place to Come To (Novel "X")
      - Holograph notes, n.d. (Box 174, Folder 3092-94)
      - Draft A: holograph, n.d. (Box 174, Folder 3095-3104)
      - Draft A: holograph, n.d. (Box 175, Folder 3105-07)
      - Draft B (incomplete): typescript, photocopy, corrected, n.d. (Box 175, Folder 3108-14)
      - Draft C: typescript and photocopy (Box 175, Folder 3115-20)
      - Draft C: typescript and photocopy (Box 176, Folder 3121-29)
      - Draft D
        - Copy 1: typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 176, Folder 3130-37)
        - Copy 2: typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 177, Folder 3138-40)
        - Copy 3: typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 177, Folder 3141-53)
      - Draft E (marked "version 2"): typescript, corrected, 1975 (Box 178, Folder 3154-64)
      - Draft F: typescript, corrected, [1976] (Box 178, Folder 3165-66)
      - Draft F: typescript, corrected, [1976] (Box 179, Folder 3167-74)
      - Draft G (incomplete): typescript, corrected, photocopy, [1972], n.d. (Box 179, Folder 3175-77)
      - Draft G (incomplete): typescript, corrected, photocopy, [1972], n.d. (Box 180, Folder 3178-81)
      - Draft H (incomplete): typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 180, Folder 3182-84)
      - Draft fragments: typescript, photocopy, n.d. (Box 180, Folder 3185-89)
      - Revision sheets, n.d. (Box 180, Folder 3190)
      - Setting typescript, [1975] (Box 181, Folder 3191-3203)
      - Page proofs
        - Copy 1 ("Master Set--1st Pass"): photocopy, corrected, n.d. (Box 181, Folder 3204-06)
        - Copy 2: photocopy, corrected, n.d. (Box 182, Folder 3207-09)
      - Page proofs (revised), 1977 (Box 182, Folder 3210-12)
      - Dummy page proofs, n.d. (Box 182, Folder 3213-18)
      - "Blues", n.d. (Box 183, Folder 3219-21)
      - Layout design, n.d. (Box 183, Folder 3222)
      - Jacket covers (proofs), n.d. (Box 183, Folder 3223)
      - Editorial suggestions (Albert Erskine), n.d. (Box 183, Folder 3224)
      - Publicity (Literary Guild), 1977 (Box 183, Folder 3226)
      - Related correspondence, 1976-77 (Box 183, Folder 3227)
      - Reviews, 1977 (Box 183, Folder 3228-30)
      - Screenplay by Julian Barry (with note by Warren), 1977 (Box 183, Folder 3231)
    - A Plea in Mitigation
      - Standard version
        - First draft (incomplete): holograph and typescript, corrected (Box 184, Folder 3232)
        - Second draft: typescript, corrected (Box 184, Folder 3233)
        - Second draft, revised (incomplete): typescript, corrected (Box 184, Folder 3234)
      - Short version
        - Typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 184, Folder 3235)
        - Typescript, carbon, corrected, n.d. (Box 184, Folder 3236)
        - Printed copy, 1966 (Box 184, Folder 3237)
    - Pondy Woods and Other Poems (unpublished collection)
      - Typescript, carbon, corrected, n.d. (Box 184, Folder 3238)
    - Portrait of a Father
      - Typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 184, Folder 3239)
      - Reviews, 1988 (Box 184, Folder 3240)
    - Problem of Knowledge (unpublished collection of poems)
      - Typescript of poems, n.d. (Box 184, Folder 3241)
    - Promises
      - Holograph and typescript texts of poems (Box 184, Folder 3242-63)
      - Typescript, carbon (incomplete; marked "sent to Allen Tate"), n.d. (Box 184, Folder 3264)
      - Typescript, corrected (for Yale Review ), 1987 (Box 184, Folder 3265)
      - Setting typescript,corrected, n.d. (Box 184, Folder 3266-67)
      - Galley proofs (author's set)
        See: Oversize, Box 302, folder 5290
      - Page proofs
        See: Oversize, Box 302, folder 5291
      - Plate proofs
        See: Oversize, Box 302, folder 5292
      - Reviews, 1957-58 (Box 184, Folder 3268-69)
    - Remember the Alamo
      - Notes (Box 185, Folder 3270)
      - Typescript (incomplete): carbon, 1956 (Box 185, Folder 3271)
    - The Rime of the Ancient Mariner
      (introduction: "A Poem of Pure Imagination")
      - Source material, 1940, 1945 (Box 185, Folder 3272-74)
      - Notes (Box 185, Folder 3275-77)
      - Draft A (first draft?): typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 185, Folder 3278)
      - Draft B (revised draft): typescript, n.d. (Box 185, Folder 3279-80)
      - Draft C (revised draft): typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 185, Folder 3281)
      - Draft D (incomplete): typescript, corrected (Box 185, Folder 3282)
      - Setting typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 185, Folder 3283-84)
      - Printed text (with Warren's corrections and comments), 1946 (Box 185, Folder 3285)
      - Critique by Frederick Pottle, 1945 (Box 185, Folder 3286)
      - Bibliography on Coleridge, n.d. (Box 185, Folder 3287)
      - "Note on Essay of AM in Selected Essays": typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 185, Folder 3288)
      - Dust jacket, n.d. (Box 186, Folder 3289)
      - Reviews, n.d. (Box 186, Folder 3290)
    - Robert Penn Warren Talking: Interviews, 1950-1978
      - Introduction by Floyd Watkins: typescript, carbon, n.d. (Box 186, Folder 3291)
      - Editorial material (Random House), 1978-80 (Box 186, Folder 3292-93)
      - Reviews, 1980 (Box 186, Folder 3294-95)
    - Rumor Verified
      - Early drafts (mixed states): holograph and typescript, corrected, 1979-80 (Box 187, Folder 3296-97)
      - Draft A (marked "third text here revised"): typescript, corrected, [1980] (Box 187, Folder 3298)
      - Draft B: typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 187, Folder 3299)
      - Draft C (marked "Master Copy"): typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 187, Folder 3300)
      - Draft D: typescript, photocopy, corrected, n.d. (Box 187, Folder 3301)
      - Draft E: typescript, photocopy, corrected, n.d. (Box 187, Folder 3302)
      - Draft F: typescript, photocopy, n.d. (Box 187, Folder 3303)
      - Draft G (incomplete): typescript, carbon, corrected, n.d. (Box 187, Folder 3304)
      - Miscellaneous pages, n.d. (Box 187, Folder 3305)
      - Front matter, n.d. (Box 188, Folder 3306)
      - Setting typescript, [1981?] (Box 188, Folder 3307)
      - Galley proofs
        See: Oversize, Box 302, folders 5293-96
      - Page proofs
        See: Oversize, Box 302, folders 5297-98
      - "Repros"
        - Copy 1, n.d. (Box 188, Folder 3308)
        - Copy 2 (cut), n.d. (Box 188, Folder 3309)
      - "Blues" (Box 188, Folder 3310)
      - Editorial material, 1981 (Box 188, Folder 3311)
      - Related material, 1981 (Box 188, Folder 3312)
      - Related correspondence, 1981 (Box 188, Folder 3312a)
      - Reviews, 1981-82 (Box 188, Folder 3313-14)
    - Segregation
      - Holograph notes, n.d. (Box 188, Folder 3315)
      - Notebooks, n.d. (Box 188, Folder 3316)
      - Draft A: typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 188, Folder 3317)
      - Draft B (incomplete): typescript, carbon, n.d. (Box 188, Folder 3318)
      - Draft C (marked "2nd revise"):
        - Copy 1: typescript, n.d. (Box 188, Folder 3319)
        - Copy 2: typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 188, Folder 3320)
      - Draft D ("South Revisited"): typescript, carbon, corrected, n.d.
        - Copy 1: typescript, carbon, corrected (Box 188, Folder 3321)
        - Copy 2: typescript, carbon, corrected (Box 188, Folder 3322)
      - Draft E (incomplete): typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 188, Folder 3323)
      - Manuscript fragments, n.d. (Box 188, Folder 3324-25)
      - Setting typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 188, Folder 3326)
      - Galley proofs
        See: Oversize, Box 303, folders 5299-5300
      - Page proofs (front matter only), n.d. (Box 189, Folder 3327)
      - Plate proofs
        See: Oversize, Box 303, folder 5301
      - Life abridgement ("Divided South Searches Its Soul")
        - Galley proofs, n.d. (Box 189, Folder 3328)
        - Printed text, [1956 Jul 9] (Box 189, Folder 3329)
        - Illustrations, n.d. (Box 189, Folder 3330)
      - Reviews, 1956 (Box 189, Folder 3331-36)
      - Miscellaneous, 1956 (Box 189, Folder 3337)
    - Selected Essays
      - Notes (Box 189, Folder 3338)
      - Preface: typescript, photocopy, n.d. (Box 189, Folder 3339)
      - Faulkner essay: typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 189, Folder 3340)
      - Setting typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 189, Folder 3341-45)
      - Essays omitted from published text: typescripts (Box 189, Folder 3346)
      - Galley proofs
        See: Oversize, box 304, folders 5302-03
      - Page proofs
        See: Oversize, Box 304, folders 5304-05
      - Plate proofs, n.d. (Box 190, Folder 3347-51)
      - Promotional material, n.d. (Box 190, Folder 3352)
      - List of recipients for review copies, n.d. (Box 190, Folder 3353)
      - Reviews, 1958 (Box 190, Folder 3354-55)
    - Selected Poems, 1923-1943
      - Holograph and typescript draft (Box 190, Folder 3356)
      - Manuscript fragments, n.d. (Box 190, Folder 3357)
      - Setting typescript, n.d. (Box 190, Folder 3358)
      - Reviews, 1941-51 (Box 190, Folder 3359)
    - Selected Poems, 1923-1975
      - Reviews (Box 190, Folder 3360)
      - Preface to Franklin Library edition: holograph, [1926] (Box 190, Folder 3361)
      - Typescripts of individual poems (not arranged), with letters from Warren, 1965-75, n.d. (Box 190, Folder 3362-64)
      - Typescript, photocopy, n.d. (Box 191, Folder 3365-67)
      - Setting typescript (with holograph preface), n.d. (Box 191, Folder 3368-75)
      - Galley proofs
        See: Oversize, Box 305, folders 5306-10
      - "Repros" (pages in order received), n.d. (Box 191, Folder 3376-79)
      - Printed text: photocopy (incomplete), [1975] (Box 192, Folder 3380)